<!--
  ~ Copyright © 2020 NHSX. All rights reserved.
  -->

<resources>
    <string name="app_name">NHS Co-Locate</string>
    <string name="location_permission">\u2022 your device’s <b>location</b>, to record places you’ve spent time in</string>
    <string name="bluetooth_permission">\u2022 <b>Bluetooth</b>, to record when your device is near others using this app</string>
    <string name="onboarding_title">Help the NHS stop the spread of coronavirus in the UK</string>
    <string name="location_rationale">Your location will not be tracked, and is needed for Bluetooth to work. Your location history and personal identity will remain protected.</string>
    <string name="explanation_link">Learn more about how it works</string>
    <string name="next_steps">You’ll be asked to consent to these permissions on the next screen.</string>
    <string name="start_now">Start Now</string>
    <string name="bluetooth_rationale">This app works using Bluetooth signals, to determine when you’re near someone else with this app. Please make sure your Bluetooth is on at all times.</string>
    <string name="app_title">Coronavirus</string>
    <string name="please_activate_bluetooth">Please activate Bluetooth</string>
    <string name="diagnosed">Have you been diagnosed with coronavirus?</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="no">No</string>
    <string name="notify">Notify</string>
    <string name="status_amber_title">You have been near someone who has coronavirus symptoms</string>
    <string name="isolate_disclaimer_title">You need to isolate yourself and stay at home</string>
    <string name="isolate_title">Help us keep others safe</string>
    <string name="isolate_message">This app has recorded all contact you’ve had with other people using this app over the past 14 days.</string>
    <string name="isolate_share">Sharing this information with the NHS means we can notify these people to take steps to keep themselves safe.</string>
    <string name="ok_title">How you can protect yourself and others</string>
    <string name="ok_disclaimer_title">You\'re okay right now</string>
    <string name="ok_disclaimer_body">This is a real-time status based on people you’ve been in contact with.\n\nYou’ll get an alert if your status changes.\n\n <b>It’s important that you tell us if you develop any new symptoms.</b></string>
    <string name="ok_symptom_title">If you develop symptoms</string>
    <string name="ok_info_content">You can stay safe by washing your hands more regularly and avoiding large gatherings of people.\n\nVisit NHS 111 for more advice on protecting yourself and people you care about.\n\nThank you for helping us slow the spread of coronavirus.</string>
    <string name="ok_symptom_content">Use our online tool to check your symptoms.</string>
    <string name="check_my_symptoms">Check my symptoms</string>
    <string name="default_notification_channel_id" translatable="false">colocate-locate</string>
    <string name="please_isolate">Please isolate</string>
    <string name="start_main_activity">Start main activity</string>
    <string name="notification_title">NHS Coronavirus</string>
    <string name="notification_text">"Someone you've been nearby recently was just diagnosed with coronavirus.\n\nYou should isolate yourself and get tested."</string>
    <string name="erro_data_submission">Something went wrong, please try again later.</string>
    <string name="main_notification_channel_name">General</string>
    <string name="registration_title">Your app is set up and ready to go</string>
    <string name="register_rationale">Keep Bluetooth and push notifications enabled for the duration of the outbreak, to help protect yourself from coronavirus.\n\nOnce the outbreak ends, you can turn off these permissions, or delete the app.</string>
    <string name="start_using_the_app">Start using the app</string>
    <string name="retry">Retry</string>
    <string name="permissions_required">This app cannot function without permissions</string>
    <string name="permission_title">Set up app permissions</string>
    <string name="bluetooth_rationale_title">Bluetooth</string>
    <string name="permission_rationale_title">Location</string>
    <string name="continue_button">Continue</string>
    <string name="registration_message">Thank you for playing your part in helping the NHS to stop the spread of coronavirus.</string>
    <string name="start_app">Start using the app</string>
    <string name="explanation_title">How the app works</string>
    <string name="explanation_how"><![CDATA[<p>This app gives you advice if you have been near someone who later develops coronavirus symptoms. The app uses your phone to detect other app users nearby.</p><p>If you think you have coronavirus symptoms you can add them in this app. The NHS will then let others know they have been near someone who has developed symptoms. This helps protect everyone and the NHS.</p><p>Your identity is not shared with other app users. The NHS will protect your identity. All information is stored securely.</p><p>Read <a href="https://www.nhs.uk/">more about the app</a>, the <a href="https://www.nhs.uk/">privacy policy</a> and all <a href="https://www.nhs.uk/">terms and conditions</a>.</p>]]></string>
    <string name="go_back">Go back</string>
    <string name="explanation_privacy">If you have coronavirus symptoms, the NHS will ask for the proximity information collected on your phone so that we can alert others that they may be at risk.\n\nThis information will be encrypted, and is only shared with the NHS. Your location history and personal identity will remain protected.</string>
    <string name="policy_terms">"Read our privacy policy and terms and conditions. "</string>
    <string name="bluetooth_battery_title">Will Bluetooth affect my phone’s battery life?</string>
    <string name="bluetooth_battery_body">This app uses low energy Bluetooth which will have minimal effect on your battery life.</string>
    <string name="mock_app_name">Debug NHS</string>
    <string name="for_debug_purposes_only">For debug purposes only.\n\nReset will clear out the registration, status, and all contact events.</string>
    <string name="notification_bluetooth_disabled_title">Please turn Bluetooth on</string>
    <string name="notification_bluetooth_disabled_text">This app can only protect you and others if Bluetooth is on all the time</string>
    <string name="notification_bluetooth_disabled_action">Enable Bluetooth</string>
    <string name="notification_location_disabled_title">Please turn Location on</string>
    <string name="notification_location_disabled_text">This app can only protect you and others if Location is on all the time</string>
    <string name="notification_location_disabled_action">Go to your Settings</string>
    <string name="started">Started %s</string>
    <string name="temperature_question">Do you have a high temperature?</string>
    <string name="temperature_description">You don\'t need a thermometer or to know a precise temperature. If you feel hot to touch on your chest or back answer \'yes\'.</string>
    <string name="cough_question">Do you have a new continuous cough?</string>
    <string name="cough_description">I have a new, continuous cough (I am coughing a lot for more than an hour, or have had 3 or more coughing episodes in 24 hours)</string>
    <string name="diagnosis_review_title">Thank you for sharing this data with the NHS.</string>
    <string name="diagnosis_review_description">Thank you for sharing this data with the NHS. We will use this information to anonymously inform people they have come into contact with covid symptoms and encourage them to self-isolate.\nThank you for helping us save lives</string>
    <string name="submit">Submit</string>
    <string name="radio_button_temperature_error">Select yes if you have a high temperature</string>
    <string name="radio_button_cough_error">Select yes if you have a continuous cough</string>
    <string name="add_my_symptoms">Add my symptoms</string>
    <string name="yes_temperature">Yes, I have a high temperature</string>
    <string name="no_temperature">No, I don’t have a high temperature</string>
    <string name="yes_cough">Yes, I have a new continuous cough</string>
    <string name="no_cough">No, I don’t have a new continuous cough</string>
    <string name="progress_one_third">1/3</string>
    <string name="progress_two_thirds">2/3</string>
    <string name="progress_half">1/2</string>
    <string name="progress_two_out_of_two">2/2</string>
    <string name="progress_three_thirds">3/3</string>
    <string name="submission_error">Submission failed. Please try again</string>
    <string name="status_latest_advice">Read what to do next</string>
    <string name="status_feeling_ok">I feel as healthy as normal</string>
    <string name="status_feeling_ok_desc">Nothing abnormal or out of the usual is going on with me</string>
    <string name="status_not_feeling_well">I feel unwell</string>
    <string name="status_not_feeling_well_desc">I have a high temperature or continuous cough and want to know what to do next</string>
    <string name="status_initial_title">Keep following the current government advice</string>
    <string name="status_red_title">Your symptoms indicate you may have coronavirus</string>
    <string name="status_red_next_steps">Next steps</string>
    <string name="need_medical_advice">If you need urgent medical advice about your coronavirus symptoms, visit</string>
    <string name="nhs_online_service">NHS Coronavirus</string>
    <string name="nhs_111_online_service">NHS 111 online coronavirus service</string>
    <string name="status_today_feeling">How are you feeling today?</string>
    <string name="registration_finalising_setup">Finalising setup…</string>
    <string name="registration_everything_is_working_ok">Everything is working OK</string>
    <string name="registration_app_setup_failed">App setup failed</string>
    <string name="post_code_title">Enter the first part of your home postcode</string>
    <string name="post_code">Post code</string>
    <string name="post_code_rationale"><![CDATA[This information will be used to help your local NHS respond to the coronavirus in your area and to understand the spread of the disease across the UK. Your postcode will <b>not</b> be used to track your location.]]></string>
    <string name="valid_post_code_is_required">Valid post code is required</string>
    <string name="coronavirus">Stop the Spread</string>
    <string name="app_rationale">This app can let you know if you may have been near someone with coronavirus symptoms (COVID-19).</string>
    <string name="back">Back</string>
    <string name="explanation_privacy_policy_and_terms_and_conditions">Read our privacy policy and terms and conditions.</string>
    <string name="notification_registration_failed_title">Your registration has failed</string>
    <string name="notification_registration_failed_text">Please open the app and select retry to complete your registration.</string>
    <string name="symptoms_date_prompt_all">When did you first start showing these symptoms?</string>
    <string name="symptoms_date_prompt_cough">When did your cough start?</string>
    <string name="symptoms_date_prompt_temperature">When did your high temperature start?</string>
    <string name="today">Today</string>
    <string name="yesterday">Yesterday</string>
    <string name="other_date">Select a different date…</string>
    <string name="start_date">Start date</string>

    <string name="close">Close</string>
    <string name="you_do_not_have_symptoms">You don’t have the primary coronavirus symptoms at this time</string>
    <string name="if_showing_other_symptoms">If you are showing other symptoms, or think you may have coronavirus, please visit</string>
    <string name="check_answers">Check your answers</string>
    <string name="i_do_temperature">I have a high temperature</string>
    <string name="i_do_not_temperature">I don\'t have a high temperature</string>
    <string name="i_do_cough">I have a new continues cough</string>
    <string name="i_do_not_cough">I don\'t have a new continuous cough</string>
    <string name="date_selection_error">Select the date from the dropdown</string>
    <string name="update_symptoms_promt">7 days ago your cough started. Please update your symptoms to view latest advice.</string>
    <string name="update_my_symptoms">Update my symptoms</string>
    <string name="no_symptoms">I no longer have symptoms</string>
    <string name="recovery_dialog_title">Start following general advice</string>
    <string name="recovery_dialog_description">Although you still have a continuous cough, you no longer need to
        self-isolate and can begin following general advice.
    </string>
    <string name="okay">Okay</string>
    <string name="enable_bluetooth_title">Your permission is needed to allow the use of Bluetooth</string>
    <string name="enable_bluetooth_rationale">This app uses battery-saving Bluetooth Low Energy to determine when it is near another phone with this app installed. For this to work, Bluetooth needs to be kept on at all times. \n\nUsing Bluetooth means that the app cannot track your location and your privacy remains protected.\n\nIf you do not give permission for Bluetooth this app will not work.\n\nTo give permission for this app to access Bluetooth, please go to Settings and allow access</string>
    <string name="enable_bluetooth">Enable Bluetooth</string>
    <string name="grant_location_permission_title">Your permission is needed to allow access to your location</string>
    <string name="grant_location_permission_rationale">This app is not using Bluetooth or your location to track you. Your personal identity will remain protected at all times.\n\nThis app uses battery-saving Bluetooth Low Energy to determine when it is near another phone with this app installed. For this to work, Bluetooth needs to be kept on at all times. \n\nIf you do not allow access to your location this app will not work.\n\nTo enable this app to work, please go to Settings and allow access:</string>
    <string name="go_to_app_settings">Go to App Settings</string>
    <string name="go_to_your_settings">Go to your Settings</string>
    <string name="enable_location_service_title">You need to enable location services on your phone</string>
    <string name="enable_location_service_rationale">To make Bluetooth work, we need you to turn on location services on your phone.\n\nThis app is not using Bluetooth or your location to track you. Your personal identity will remain protected at all times.\n\nThis app uses battery-saving Bluetooth Low Energy to determine when it is near another phone with this app installed. For this to work, Bluetooth needs to be kept on at all times. \n\nIf you do not enable location services on your phone this app will not work.\n\nTo enable this app to work, please go to Settings and enable location services:</string>
    <string name="follow_until">Follow this advice until %1$s</string>
    <string name="status_description_01">If you don’t have any symptoms, there’s no need to do anything right now.</string>
    <string name="status_description_02">Feel free to use other apps as normal and you’ll be notified if your advice changes.</string>
    <string name="status_description_03">If you develop symptoms, please come back to this app.</string>
    <string name="re_enable_bluetooth_title">Please turn your Bluetooth back on</string>
    <string name="re_enable_bluetooth_rationale">This app works only if your Bluetooth is on at all times.\n\n%1$s works using Bluetooth signals, to determine when you have been near someone else with this app who shows symptoms of Coronavirus. %1$s can alert you or others that may be at risk.</string>
    <string name="re_enable_location_title">Turn on location services on your phone to continue</string>
    <string name="re_enable_location_rationale">To make Bluetooth work, we also need you to turn on location services. Your location will not be tracked. Your location and personal identity will remain protected.\n\nTo enable your location you need to turn on your location services on your phone.\n\n%1$s works using Bluetooth signals, to determine when you have been near someone else with this app who shows symptoms of Coronavirus.</string>
    <string name="re_allow_location_permission_title">Allow this app to access your location to continue</string>
    <string name="re_allow_location_permission_rationale">To make Bluetooth work, we also need you to turn on location services and give the app permission to use it. Your location will not be tracked. Your location and personal identity will remain protected.\n\nTo enable your location permissions you need to go to your Settings and allow this app to access location services.\n\n%1$s works using Bluetooth signals, to determine when you have been near someone else with this app who shows symptoms of Coronavirus.</string>
    <string name="view_reference_code">View reference code</string>
    <string name="reference_code">Reference code</string>
    <string name="loading">Loading…</string>
    <string name="error">Error</string>
    <string name="post_code_example">Example: CE1B</string>
    <string name="post_code_rationale_title">Why do we need this?</string>
</resources>
