<!--
  ~ Copyright © 2020 NHSX. All rights reserved.
  -->

<resources>
    <string name="app_name">NHS Co-Locate</string>
    <string name="location_permission">\u2022 your device’s <b>location</b>, to record places you’ve spent time in</string>
    <string name="bluetooth_permission">\u2022 <b>Bluetooth</b>, to record when your device is near others using this app</string>
    <string name="onboarding_title">Help the NHS stop the spread of coronavirus in the UK</string>
    <string name="permission_rationale">Your location will not be stored, and is needed for Bluetooth to work</string>
    <string name="explanation_link"><u>Learn more about how it works</u></string>
    <string name="next_steps">You’ll be asked to consent to these permissions on the next screen.</string>
    <string name="start_now">Start Now</string>
    <string name="bluetooth_rationale">The app works using bluetooth signals, to determine when you’re near someone else with this app</string>
    <string name="app_title">Coronavirus Tracing</string>
    <string name="please_activate_bluetooth">Please activate Bluetooth</string>
    <string name="diagnosed">Have you been diagnosed with coronavirus?</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="no">No</string>
    <string name="notify">Notify</string>
    <string name="potential_disclaimer_title">You need to stay at home and help us keep others safe</string>
    <string name="isolate_disclaimer_title">You need to isolate yourself and stay at home</string>
    <string name="isolate_title">Help us keep others safe</string>
    <string name="isolate_message">This app has recorded all contact you’ve had with other people using this app over the past 14 days.</string>
    <string name="isolate_share">Sharing this information with the NHS means we can notify these people to take steps to keep themselves safe.</string>
    <string name="ok_title">How you can protect yourself and others</string>
    <string name="ok_disclaimer_title">You\'re okay right now</string>
    <string name="ok_disclaimer_body">This is a real-time status based on people you’ve been in contact with.\n\nYou’ll get an alert if your status changes.\n\n <b>It’s important that you tell us if you develop any new symptoms.</b></string>
    <string name="ok_symptom_title">If you develop symptoms</string>
    <string name="ok_info_content">You can stay safe by washing your hands more regularly and avoiding large gatherings of people.\n\nVisit NHS 111 for more advice on protecting yourself and people you care about.\n\nThank you for helping us slow the spread of coronavirus.</string>
    <string name="ok_symptom_content">Use our online tool to check your symptoms.</string>
    <string name="check_my_symptoms">Check my symptoms</string>
    <string name="default_notification_channel_id" translatable="false">colocate-locate</string>
    <string name="please_isolate">Please isolate</string>
    <string name="start_main_activity">Start main activity</string>
    <string name="notification_title">NHS Coronavirus</string>
    <string name="notification_text">"Someone you've been nearby recently was just diagnosed with coronavirus.\n\nYou should isolate yourself and get tested."</string>
    <string name="successfull_data_upload">You have successfully shared you contact data with NHS.</string>
    <string name="erro_data_submission">Something went wrong, please try again later.</string>
    <string name="main_notification_channel_name">NHS Colocate</string>
    <string name="registration_title">Your app is set up and ready to go</string>
    <string name="register_rationale">Keep Bluetooth and push notifications enabled for the duration of the outbreak, to help protect yourself from coronavirus.\n\nOnce the outbreak ends, you can turn off these permissions, or delete the app.</string>
    <string name="start_using_the_app">Start using the app</string>
    <string name="retry">Retry</string>
    <string name="permissions_required">This app cannot function without permissions</string>
    <string name="permission_title">Set up app permissions</string>
    <string name="bluetooth_rationale_title">Bluetooth</string>
    <string name="permission_rationale_title">Location</string>
    <string name="continue_button">Continue</string>
    <string name="registration_message">Thank you for playing your part in helping the NHS to stop the spread of coronavirus.</string>
    <string name="start_app">Start using the app</string>
    <string name="explanation_title">How the app works</string>
    <string name="explanation_how">The app uses your phone’s low energy Bluetooth to detect if you’ve been near someone else with this app.</string>
    <string name="go_back">Go back</string>
    <string name="explanation_privacy">If you have coronavirus symptoms, the NHS will ask for the proximity information collected on your phone so that we can alert others that they may be at risk.\n\nThis information will be encrypted, and is only shared with the NHS. Your location history and personal identity will remain protected.</string>
    <string name="policy_terms">"Read our privacy policy and terms and conditions. "</string>
    <string name="bluetooth_battery_title">Will Bluetooth affect my phone’s battery life?</string>
    <string name="bluetooth_battery_body">This app uses low energy Bluetooth which will have minimal effect on your battery life.</string>
    <string name="mock_app_name">Debug NHS</string>
    <string name="for_debug_purposes_only">For debug purposes only.\n\nReset will clear out the registration, status, and all contact events.</string>
</resources>
