<!--
  ~ Copyright © 2020 NHSX. All rights reserved.
  -->

<resources>
    <string name="app_name">NHS COVID-19</string>
    <string name="app_title">COVID-19</string>
    <string name="onboarding_title">This NHS app does three things for you:</string>
    <string name="onboarding_first_bullet_text">It lets you know if you have been near someone who now has coronavirus</string>
    <string name="onboarding_second_bullet_text">It links you to up-to-date guidance on coronavirus that is relevant to your situation</string>
    <string name="onboarding_third_bullet_text">It lets you book a test if you have certain symptoms of coronavirus</string>
    <string name="one">1</string>
    <string name="two">2</string>
    <string name="three">3</string>
    <string name="location_rationale">You will not be tracked and your personal identity and location history will
        remain protected at all times. On an Android phone, your location permission is needed for Bluetooth to work.
    </string>
    <string name="explanation_link">
        <u>Learn more about how the app works</u>
    </string>
    <string name="bluetooth_rationale">This app uses battery-saving Bluetooth Low Energy to determine when it is near
        another phone with this app. For this app to work, Bluetooth needs to be kept on at all times.
    </string>
    <string name="status_exposed_title">You have been near someone who has tested positive for coronavirus. Please self-isolate.</string>
    <string name="status_positive_test_title">Your test result indicates  you  have coronavirus. Please isolate yourself and your household.</string>
    <string name="default_notification_channel_id" translatable="false">colocate-locate</string>
    <string name="default_notification_channel_name">General</string>
    <string name="foreground_service_channel_id" translatable="false">colocate-foreground-service</string>
    <string name="foreground_service_channel_name">Application service</string>
    <string name="permissions_and_access_channel_id" translatable="false">colocate-permissions-and-access</string>
    <string name="permissions_and_access_channel_name">Bluetooth and location reminders</string>
    <string name="contact_and_checkin_channel_id" translatable="false">colocate-contact-and-checkin</string>
    <string name="contact_and_checkin_channel_name">Coronavirus notifications</string>
    <string name="start_main_activity">Start main activity</string>
    <string name="contact_alert_notification_title">Your advice has changed</string>
    <string name="contact_alert_notification_text">Please open the app to learn what to do next. Your help saves lives.</string>
    <string name="test_result_notification_title">Your test result has arrived</string>
    <string name="test_result_notification_text">Your test result has arrived. Please open the app to learn what to do next. You have been sent an email or text with more information.</string>
    <string name="permission_title">Set up app permissions</string>
    <string name="bluetooth_rationale_title">Bluetooth</string>
    <string name="permission_rationale_title">Location</string>
    <string name="continue_button">Continue</string>
    <string name="explanation_title">How the app works</string>
    <string name="explanation_how">
        <![CDATA[
        <p>
        This app gives you advice if you have been near someone who tested positive for coronavirus
        after reporting symptoms. The app uses your phone to detect other app users nearby.
        </p>
        <p>
        If you think you have coronavirus symptoms you can add them in this app. If you then test
        positive, the NHS will let others know they have been near someone who has tested positive
        for coronavirus.
        </p>
        <p>
        Your identity is not shared with other app users. The NHS will protect your identity. All
        information is stored securely.
        </p>]]></string>
    <string name="explanation_more_about_the_app">
        <u>More about the app</u>
    </string>
    <string name="explanation_privacy_notice"><u>Privacy notice</u></string>
    <string name="explanation_terms_of_use"><u>Terms of use</u></string>
    <string name="go_back">Go back</string>
    <string name="for_debug_purposes_only">For debug purposes only. Your sonar Id is:</string>
    <string name="notification_bluetooth_disabled_title">Please turn Bluetooth on</string>
    <string name="notification_bluetooth_disabled_text">This app can only protect you and others if Bluetooth is on all the time</string>
    <string name="notification_bluetooth_disabled_action">Enable Bluetooth</string>
    <string name="notification_location_disabled_title">Please turn Location on</string>
    <string name="notification_location_disabled_text">This app can only protect you and others if Location is on all the time</string>
    <string name="notification_location_disabled_action">Go to your Settings</string>
    <!-- Questionnaire -->
    <string name="temperature_question">Do you have a high temperature (fever)?</string>
    <string name="temperature_question_simplified">Do you have a high temperature (fever)?</string>
    <string name="temperature_description">This means that you feel hot to touch on your chest or back (you do not need to measure your temperature).\n\nYour response to this question helps us decide whether you need to book a coronavirus test.</string>
    <string name="temperature_description_simplified">This means that you feel hot to touch on your chest or back (you do not need to measure your temperature)</string>
    <string name="yes_temperature">Yes, I have a high temperature</string>
    <string name="no_temperature">No, I do not have a high temperature</string>
    <string name="cough_question">Do you have a new continuous cough?</string>
    <string name="cough_question_simplified">Do you have a continuous cough?</string>
    <string name="cough_description">This means coughing a lot for more than an hour, or 3 or more coughing episodes in 24 hours (if you usually have a cough, it may be worse than usual).\n\nYour response to this question helps us decide whether you need to book a coronavirus test.</string>
    <string name="cough_description_simplified">This means coughing a lot for more than an hour, or 3 or more coughing episodes in 24 hours (if you usually have a cough, it may be worse than usual).</string>
    <string name="yes_new_cough">Yes, I have a new continuous cough</string>
    <string name="no_new_cough">No, I do not have a new continuous cough</string>
    <string name="yes_cough">Yes, I have a continuous cough</string>
    <string name="no_cough">No, I do not have a continuous cough</string>
    <string name="anosmia_question">Have you had a new loss or change to your sense of smell or taste?</string>
    <string name="anosmia_question_simplified">Have you had a loss or change to your sense of smell or taste?</string>
    <string name="anosmia_description">This means you have noticed you cannot smell or taste anything, or things smell or taste different to normal.\n\nYour response to this question helps us decide whether you need to book a coronavirus test.</string>
    <string name="anosmia_description_simplified">This means you have noticed you cannot smell or taste anything, or things smell or taste different to normal.</string>
    <string name="yes_anosmia">Yes, I have a new loss or change to my sense of smell or taste</string>
    <string name="no_anosmia">No, I do not have a new loss or change to my sense of smell or taste</string>
    <string name="sneeze_question">Do you have a runny nose, feel feverish or suffer from sneezing?</string>
    <string name="sneeze_question_simplified">Do you have a runny nose, feel feverish or suffer from sneezing?</string>
    <string name="sneeze_description">Runny nose: this means your nose is more runny than usual.\n\nFeeling feverish: this means you have sore or aching muscles, feel unusually tired, have a headache or are shivering or feeling warm or hot.\n\nSneezing: this means you are sneezing more than normal, not caused by any known allergy.\n\nYour response to this question helps the NHS better understand coronavirus.</string>
    <string name="sneeze_description_simplified">Runny nose: this means your nose is more runny than usual.\n\nFeeling feverish: this means you have sore or aching muscles, feel unusually tired, have a headache or are shivering or feeling warm or hot.\n\nSneezing: this means you are sneezing more than normal, not caused by any known allergy.</string>
    <string name="stomach_question">Do you have diarrhoea, nausea, vomiting or have a loss of appetite?</string>
    <string name="stomach_question_simplified">Do you have diarrhoea, nausea, vomiting or have a loss of appetite?</string>
    <string name="stomach_description">Diarrhoea: this means your poo has been more runny or watery than normal.\n\nNausea: this means you are feeling sick.\n\nVomiting: this means you have been sick more than once.\n\nLoss of appetite: this means you are not feeling hungry, or are not eating as much as normal.\n\nYour response to this question helps the NHS better understand coronavirus.</string>
    <string name="stomach_description_simplified">Diarrhoea: this means your poo has been more runny or watery than normal.\n\nNausea: this means you are feeling sick.\n\nVomiting: this means you have been sick more than once.\n\nLoss of appetite: this means you are not feeling hungry, or are not eating as much as normal.</string>
    <string name="yes_to_symptoms">Yes, I have at least one of these symptoms</string>
    <string name="no_to_symptoms">No, I don\'t have any of these symptoms</string>
    <!-- /Questionnaire -->
    <string name="submit">Submit</string>
    <string name="radio_button_symptoms_error">Select yes if you have at least one of these symptoms</string>
    <string name="radio_button_anosmia_error">Select yes if you have recently lost your sense of smell or taste</string>
    <string name="radio_button_temperature_error">Select yes if you have a high temperature</string>
    <string name="radio_button_cough_error">Select yes if you have a continuous cough</string>
    <string name="add_my_symptoms">Add my symptoms</string>
    <string name="progress_one_sixth">1/6</string>
    <string name="progress_two_sixth">2/6</string>
    <string name="progress_three_sixth">3/6</string>
    <string name="progress_four_sixth">4/6</string>
    <string name="progress_five_sixth">5/6</string>
    <string name="progress_six_sixth">6/6</string>
    <string name="progress_one_fifth">1/5</string>
    <string name="progress_two_fifth">2/5</string>
    <string name="progress_three_fifth">3/5</string>
    <string name="progress_four_fifth">4/5</string>
    <string name="progress_five_fifth">5/5</string>
    <string name="status_latest_advice">
        <u>Read current advice</u>
    </string>
    <string name="status_what_to_do">
        <u>Read what to do next</u>
    </string>
    <string name="status_not_feeling_well">I feel unwell</string>
    <string name="status_not_feeling_well_desc">I might have symptoms of coronavirus and want to know what to do next.</string>
    <string name="status_initial_title">Follow the current advice to stop the spread of coronavirus</string>
    <string name="status_symptomatic_title">Your symptoms indicate you may have coronavirus. Please isolate yourself and your household and book a test.</string>
    <string name="need_medical_advice">Find your NHS services for your part of the country</string>
    <string name="nhs_online_service"><u>NHS Coronavirus</u></string>
    <string name="tablet_information_url"><u>Information on the use of tablets</u></string>
    <string name="nhs_111_online_service"><u>NHS 111 online coronavirus service</u></string>
    <string name="apply_for_test_now_url"><u>Book a coronavirus test now</u></string>
    <string name="status_today_feeling">How are you feeling today?</string>
    <string name="registration_finalising_setup">Finalising setup…</string>
    <string name="registration_everything_is_working_ok">The app is working properly</string>
    <string name="post_code_title">Enter the first part of your home postcode</string>
    <string name="post_code_rationale"><![CDATA[This information will be used to help your local NHS respond to the coronavirus in your area and to understand the spread of the disease across the UK. Your postcode will <b>not</b> be used to track your location.]]></string>
    <string name="valid_post_code_is_required">Please enter the first part of a valid postcode. For example: PO30, E2, M1, EH1, L36</string>
    <string name="app_rationale">This app can let you know if you may have been near someone with coronavirus symptoms (COVID-19).</string>
    <string name="symptoms_date_prompt_all">When did you first start showing any of these symptoms?</string>
    <string name="today">Today</string>
    <string name="yesterday">Yesterday</string>
    <string name="other_date">Select a different date…</string>
    <string name="start_date">Start date</string>

    <string name="close">Close</string>
    <string name="you_do_not_have_symptoms">You do not appear to have coronavirus symptoms</string>
    <string name="if_showing_other_symptoms">If you are showing other symptoms, or think you may have coronavirus, please visit</string>
    <string name="check_answers">Check your answers</string>
    <string name="i_do_temperature">I have a high temperature</string>
    <string name="i_do_not_temperature">I don\'t have a high temperature</string>
    <string name="i_do_cough">I have a new continuous cough</string>
    <string name="i_do_not_cough">I don\'t have a new continuous cough</string>
    <string name="i_do_anosmia">I have recently lost my sense of smell</string>
    <string name="i_do_not_anosmia">I have not recently lost my sense of smell</string>
    <string name="i_do_sneeze">I have at least one of these symptoms: a runny nose, feeling feverish or sneezing</string>
    <string name="i_do_not_sneeze">I don\'t have any of these symptoms: a runny nose, feeling feverish or sneezing</string>
    <string name="i_do_stomach">I have at least one of these symptoms: diarrhoea, nausea, vomiting or loss of appetite</string>
    <string name="i_do_not_stomach">I don\'t have any of these symptoms: diarrhoea, nausea, vomiting or loss of appetite</string>
    <string name="date_selection_error">Select the date you first started showing any of these symptoms</string>
    <string name="update_symptoms_prompt">Please update your symptoms to view your latest advice.</string>
    <string name="update_symptoms_prompt_with_negative_test">Thank you for getting tested. You have been sent an email with more information.\n\nIf you are having symptoms, please update your symptoms to see the latest advice for you. If you do not have any symptoms, you can now follow the advice for the general public.</string>
    <string name="update_my_symptoms">Update my symptoms</string>
    <string name="no_symptoms">I no longer have symptoms</string>
    <string name="recovery_dialog_title">Thank you for updating your symptoms</string>
    <string name="recovery_dialog_description">Although you still have some symptoms you can now stop self-isolating and follow the current advice for the general public.</string>
    <string name="okay">Okay</string>
    <string name="enable_bluetooth_title">Your permission is needed to allow the use of Bluetooth</string>
    <string name="enable_bluetooth_rationale">This app uses battery-saving Bluetooth Low Energy to determine when it is near another phone with this app installed. For this to work, Bluetooth needs to be kept on at all times. \n\nUsing Bluetooth means that the app cannot track your location and your privacy remains protected.\n\nIf you do not give permission for Bluetooth this app will not work.\n\nTo give permission for this app to access Bluetooth, please go to Settings and allow access</string>
    <string name="enable_bluetooth">Enable Bluetooth</string>
    <string name="grant_location_permission_title">Your permission is needed to allow access to your location all the time</string>
    <string name="grant_location_permission_title_pre_10">Your permission is needed to allow access to your location</string>
    <string name="grant_location_permission_rationale">This app does not use your location to track you. Your personal identity will remain protected at all times.\n\nThis app uses battery-saving Bluetooth Low Energy to determine when it is near another phone with this app installed. For this app to work, Bluetooth needs to be kept on at all times.\n\nOn an Android phone, your location permission needs to be set to “Allow all the time” for Bluetooth Low Energy to work.\n\nTo enable this app to work, please go to App Settings > Permissions and allow access:</string>
    <string name="grant_location_permission_rationale_pre_10">This app does not use your location to track you. Your personal identity will remain protected at all times.\n\nThis app uses battery-saving Bluetooth Low Energy to determine when it is near another phone with this app installed. For this app to work, Bluetooth needs to be kept on at all times.\n\nOn an Android phone, your location permission is needed for Bluetooth Low Energy to work.\n\nTo enable this app to work, please go to App Settings > Permissions and allow access:</string>
    <string name="go_to_app_settings">Go to App Settings</string>
    <string name="go_to_your_settings">Go to your Settings</string>
    <string name="enable_location_service_title">You need to enable location services on your phone</string>
    <string name="enable_location_service_rationale">To make Bluetooth work, we need you to turn on location services on your phone.\n\nThis app is not using Bluetooth or your location to track you. Your personal identity will remain protected at all times.\n\nThis app uses battery-saving Bluetooth Low Energy to determine when it is near another phone with this app installed. For this to work, Bluetooth needs to be kept on at all times. \n\nIf you do not enable location services on your phone this app will not work.\n\nTo enable this app to work, please go to Settings and enable location services:</string>
    <string name="follow_until">Please follow the advice below until </string>
    <string name="follow_until_symptomatic_pre">On %1$s </string>
    <string name="follow_until_symptomatic"> this app will notify you to update your symptoms. Please read your full advice below.</string>
    <string name="status_description_01">If you do not have any symptoms, there’s no need to do anything right now. If you develop symptoms, please come back to this app.</string>
    <string name="status_description_02">Feel free to use other apps as normal and you’ll be notified if your advice changes.</string>
    <string name="status_description_03">If you develop symptoms, please come back to this app.</string>
    <string name="re_enable_bluetooth_title">Please turn your Bluetooth back on</string>
    <string name="re_enable_bluetooth_rationale">This app works only if your Bluetooth is on at all times.\n\n%1$s works
        using Bluetooth signals, to determine when you have been near someone else with this app who shows symptoms of
        coronavirus. %1$s can alert you or others that may be at risk.
    </string>
    <string name="re_enable_location_title">Turn on location services on your phone to continue</string>
    <string name="re_enable_location_rationale">To make Bluetooth work, we also need you to turn on location services.
        Your location will not be tracked. Your location and personal identity will remain protected.\n\nTo enable your
        location you need to turn on your location services on your phone.\n\n%1$s works using Bluetooth signals, to
        determine when you have been near someone else with this app who shows symptoms of coronavirus.
    </string>
    <string name="re_allow_location_permission_title">Allow this app to access your location to continue</string>
    <string name="re_allow_location_permission_rationale">To make Bluetooth work, we also need you to turn on location
        services and give the app permission to use it. Your location will not be tracked. Your location and personal
        identity will remain protected.\n\nTo enable your location permissions you need to go to your Settings and allow
        this app to access location services.\n\n%1$s works using Bluetooth signals, to determine when you have been
        near someone else with this app who shows symptoms of coronavirus.
    </string>
    <string name="testing_information">Testing information</string>
    <string name="reference_code">Reference code</string>
    <string name="loading">Loading…</string>
    <string name="error">Error</string>
    <string name="post_code_example">Example: CE1B</string>
    <string name="post_code_rationale_title">Why do we need this?</string>
    <string name="enable_permissions">Enable permissions</string>
    <string name="notification_action_open_app">Open App</string>
    <string name="checkin_notification_title">How are you feeling today?</string>
    <string name="checkin_notification_text">Please open the app to update your symptoms and view your latest advice.
        Your help saves lives.
    </string>
    <string name="device_not_supported_title">Your phone does not support Bluetooth Low Energy sufficiently for this app to work</string>
    <string name="device_not_supported_rationale">We continue to validate and expand the number of mobile devices capable of using the NHS COVID-19 app. Find more information on Bluetooth Low Energy here:</string>
    <string name="confirm_diagnosis_text_1">The information you have provided will be used to help protect your community and the NHS. The NHS needs accurate data on the number of people with symptoms.</string>
    <string name="confirm_diagnosis_text_2">Together we can help save lives, protect the NHS, and stop the spread of coronavirus in the UK.</string>
    <string name="guidance_for_workplace">Guidance for your workplace</string>
    <string name="high_temperature">High temperature</string>
    <string name="continuous_cough">Continuous cough</string>
    <string name="info">Link to more information about NHS COVID-19 app</string>
    <string name="please_book_test">Please book a coronavirus test immediately. Write down your reference code and phone</string>
    <string name="test_booking_number"><u>0800 540 4900</u></string>
    <string name="page_1_of_6">Page 1 of 6</string>
    <string name="page_2_of_6">Page 2 of 6</string>
    <string name="page_3_of_6">Page 3 of 6</string>
    <string name="page_4_of_6">Page 4 of 6</string>
    <string name="page_5_of_6">Page 5 of 6</string>
    <string name="page_6_of_6">Page 6 of 6</string>
    <string name="page_1_of_5">Page 1 of 5</string>
    <string name="page_2_of_5">Page 2 of 5</string>
    <string name="page_3_of_5">Page 3 of 5</string>
    <string name="page_4_of_5">Page 4 of 5</string>
    <string name="page_5_of_5">Page 5 of 5</string>
    <string name="more_information">More information</string>
    <string name="submit_confirmation">I confirm that the information I have entered is accurate</string>
    <string name="please_confirm_the_information">Please confirm that the information you have entered is accurate</string>
    <string name="tablet_support_title">This app is made for mobile smartphones</string>
    <string name="tablet_support_description">Your device seems to be a tablet. This app is only available for smartphones because the app is only effective if you have it on a device that is with you all the time when you go out. Please install the app on your smartphone.</string>
    <string name="enable_notifications_text">You will not receive important notifications regarding changes in your advice unless you allow notifications in your Settings.</string>
    <string name="enable_notifications_title">Enable notifications</string>
    <string name="timestamp">Timestamp %1$s</string>
    <string name="txpower">TxPower: \nAdvertised = %1$d \nProtocol = %2$d</string>
    <string name="apply_for_test_now">Book a coronavirus test now</string>
    <string name="apply_for_test_desc">You can now book a coronavirus test for you and other people in your household. This test will tell you whether you currently have coronavirus or not.</string>
    <string name="apply_for_test_need_ref">In order for this app to receive your test result, please write down or copy into the clipboard this 8-digit app reference code as you will be asked for it later.</string>
    <string name="get_tested">Get tested</string>
    <string name="reference_code_title">Information about testing</string>
    <string name="reference_code_when_1">When you need a test</string>
    <string name="reference_code_description_1">If you have symptoms let this app know and it can help you order a coronavirus test.</string>
    <string name="reference_code_when_2">When you don\’t need a test</string>
    <string name="reference_code_description_2">You do not need a test if you have been near someone who has developed symptoms or tested positive for coronavirus, unless you have symptoms yourself.</string>
    <string name="reference_code_linking">Linking a test to this app</string>
    <string name="reference_code_app">Your app reference code</string>
    <string name="connect_to_internet">Please connect your phone to the internet to see the app reference code.</string>
    <string name="reference_code_description_3">In order for this app to receive your test result, you will be asked for this 8-digit app reference code later.</string>
    <string name="copy">Copy</string>
    <string name="copied">Copied</string>
    <string name="latest_guidance"><u>Latest guidance for your workplace</u></string>
    <string name="latest_workplace_guidance">Read the latest guidance for your workplace</string>
    <string name="workplace_guidance_info">The guidance on GOV.UK is specific to the industry you work in and helps you understand how to work safely during the coronavirus pandemic.</string>
    <string name="healt_and_care_workers_title">If you are a health and care worker:</string>
    <string name="healt_and_care_workers_description">Turn off your Bluetooth when you put on your personal protective equipment provided for you by your employer. Your interactions at work should not be captured when you are wearing personal protective equipment.</string>
    <string name="next_steps">Next Steps</string>
    <string name="read_current_advice_for_you">Read current advice for you</string>
    <string name="read_current_advice">Read current advice</string>
    <string name="symptomatic_state_advice_info">If you develop symptoms, please come back to this app.</string>
    <string name="more_options">More Options</string>
    <string name="app_version">App version:</string>
    <string name="negative_test_result_title">Your test result indicates that you do not have coronavirus</string>
    <string name="negative_test_result_description">Thank you for getting tested. View your current advice based on your results. You have been sent an email or text with more information.</string>
    <string name="current_advice_title">Read and follow advice specific to your situation</string>
    <string name="current_advice_desc_simple">The advice below is up-to-date and specific to your situation. Please follow this advice.</string>
    <string name="current_advice_desc_with_date">The advice below is up-to-date and specific to your situation. Please follow this advice until %1$s </string>
    <string name="read_specific_advice_for_you"><u>Read specific advice for you</u></string>
    <string name="positive_test_result_title">Your test result indicates that you have coronavirus</string>
    <string name="positive_test_result_description">Thank you for getting tested. View your current advice based on your results. You have been sent an email with more information.</string>
    <string name="invalid_test_result_title">Your test result was unclear</string>
    <string name="invalid_test_result_description">Thank you for getting tested. However, due to an unclear test result your advice has not been changed. Please book another test. You have been sent an email with more information.</string>
    <string name="medical_emergency_call">If you have a medical emergency, please call 999. If you require medical help near you, please go to 111 online.</string>
</resources>
